http://www.glason.com.au/privacy-policy

HomeLeave A ReviewAbout UsServicesFactory and Building Cleaning ServicesPaint & Repairs – Interior & Exterior SurfacesPedestrian Safety – Slips PreventionAlgae & Mould RemovalGraffiti RemovalRoof CleaningDriveway Cleaning & SealingHouse Washing - Interior & ExteriorHigh Pressure CleaningStrata Property & Body Corporate MaintenanceALGAE REMOVALDRIVEWAY CLEANINGGRAFFITI REMOVALHOUSE WASHING - Interior & ExteriorMOULD REMOVALPOWER CLEANING - Pressure WashingROTARY CLEANINGProductsHandy TipsClientsGalleryShopContact Us
Privacy Policy
HomeLeave A ReviewAbout UsServicesFactory and Building Cleaning ServicesPaint & Repairs – Interior & Exterior SurfacesPedestrian Safety – Slips PreventionAlgae & Mould RemovalGraffiti RemovalRoof CleaningDriveway Cleaning & SealingHouse Washing - Interior & ExteriorHigh Pressure CleaningStrata Property & Body Corporate MaintenanceALGAE REMOVALDRIVEWAY CLEANINGGRAFFITI REMOVALHOUSE WASHING - Interior & ExteriorMOULD REMOVALPOWER CLEANING - Pressure WashingROTARY CLEANINGProductsHandy TipsClientsGalleryShopContact Us
1800 452 766
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or Smart Web Solutions.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).
To process transactions: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To send periodic emails: The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
http://www.centralcoastpressurecleaning.com.au/contact.htm
Unit 17/4 Merinee Road
West Gosford, NSW 2250
Australia
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
1800 452 766
This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support. Compare Rhino Support to Zendesk and save!
The Glason®Group pty ltdCall Toll Free - 1800 GLASON (1800 452 766) All Areas for Free Quote Phone (02) 4323 7792 Email: Click Here
